[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "The ________ is the layer of air that surrounds the Earth.",
      "options": [
        "Hydrosphere",
        "Biosphere",
        "Atmosphere",
        "Lithosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "The segment of the environment that includes all water bodies is called the ________.",
      "options": [
        "Lithosphere",
        "Atmosphere",
        "Biosphere",
        "Hydrosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "The ________ provides oxygen for humans and animals to breathe.",
      "options": [
        "Hydrosphere",
        "Biosphere",
        "Lithosphere",
        "Atmosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "The land we live on is part of the ________.",
      "options": [
        "Biosphere",
        "Lithosphere",
        "Hydrosphere",
        "Atmosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Humans, animals, and plants are part of the ________.",
      "options": [
        "Biosphere",
        "Hydrosphere",
        "Lithosphere",
        "Atmosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "The Amazon rainforest is an example of the ________.",
      "options": [
        "Atmosphere",
        "Biosphere",
        "Hydrosphere",
        "Lithosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Oceans, rivers, and lakes belong to the ________.",
      "options": [
        "Lithosphere",
        "Hydrosphere",
        "Atmosphere",
        "Biosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Mountains, valleys, and soil are part of the ________.",
      "options": [
        "Lithosphere",
        "Biosphere",
        "Atmosphere",
        "Hydrosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "The process of rain formation occurs in the ________.",
      "options": [
        "Lithosphere",
        "Biosphere",
        "Hydrosphere",
        "Atmosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Underground water is part of the ________.",
      "options": [
        "Biosphere",
        "Hydrosphere",
        "Lithosphere",
        "Atmosphere"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    }
]
  